







Summary

Jump to Section

Proven leadership in developing a global team that focuses on the client experience. Passionate problem solver who craves challenging situations. Collaborative and able to work with all levels of personnel within an organization. Tenacious and committed to results. Dedicated with a track record of availability and reliability. I have an excellent track record of not only managing and driving cadence of incidents/projects to resolution but also developing others to move in the direction to succeed.

Work Experience

• Atmecs Technologies India Pvt Ltd as Technical Lead (Major Incident Management) Mar 2019 to Till Date

Integrated two separate teams and created the Major Incident Management group.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Leading a 24/7 globally based team providing major incident management & communication for enterprise clients. Developed ITIL-based processes and procedures for a multi-facet organization with various of amounts products and support requirements

Constant focus on continuous improvement. Developed KPIs, and established mentoring program, and monthly mock

Developed and lead significant improvements methods for providing client communication in times of major outages that impact either individual clients or infrastructure events impacting multiple clients

Dedicated to educating and committed to the quality of the team's communication, leadership, and personal knowledge of the various products and technologies supported by ATMECS

Client focused. Have developed a culture within my team to have that same mentality, that also extends to our internal user base.

Collaborating with multiple teams both within operations and our account management groups to have adherence to major incident management processes and taking feedback in order to better support those groups in times of major incidents

Capgemini Technology Services India Limited as Associate Consultant (Major Incident

Management)

Feb 2017 to Mar 2019

Dedicated advocate of the client.

Strong troubleshooting and problem solving skills.

Provided oversight and management for day to day operations and client speci c projects.

Performed Incident, Change, & Problem Management.

Provided 24/7 support for major incidents/outages.

Excellent communication skills. Able to balance client advocacy with company processes to ensure both parties achieve

desired results.

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld Ability to understand highly technical information and breakdown that information in an effective manner to all levels within a client's organization.

Collaborated with our global operational teams to prioritize supporting my clients objectives.

DreamWorks Animation SKG India as Network Operations Administrator Aug 2016 to Feb 2017

Oversee day to day operations of the Network and Datacenter Operations.

Oversee Incident Management and Disaster Recovery. I would drive issues to resolution

Monitor Network connections, performance, Studio Pipeline, and work to resolve issues via the monitoring tools.

Monitor Server status and work to resolve issues via various monitoring tools and restart servers as needed. Implement changes and make sure they are completed successfully and on time.

Work with critical infrastructure components and other systems through Remote PC access to troubleshoot potential issues.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Loyola College, Chennai in 2013

PG: PG Diploma (Information System Management) from Alliance Business Academy, bangalore in 2020

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Networking			

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Tamil				
Malayalam				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary
Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.